For Manan Desai Chirayu Mistry Deep Vaidya
and Viraj
[Appreciation]
How are you going?
Everything is all right,
yes, thank you, thank you, everyone, thank you so much,
friends, you must know Viraj Ghelani
and Viraj Ghelani has been creating content for the last few years
and he has
done a lot of good work, especially
for the Gujarati community, he has enjoyed a lot of entertainment
and now he is also coming in a feature film.
Please watch another work, do
n't just leave it at that. Go and watch it. Everyone, be ready
because the way these people
shout Anupama, Anupama, now Jamkudi will do Jamkudi, go and see, you will
walk for me. I do
n't like letting Anupama do anything. My
family likes it. Now don't say that. If she has a
ticket, just tell me I love Anupama,
my wallpaper is Anupama on my phone. Now,
tell me a video of her.
I saw the beer with the biceps, who was with the beer,
brother, sir, that one with his forehead, God is the one who gave it to me, and that
real life noble head, have you ever spoken to him in real
life? I met him for the first time, and
I said to him, "It's all great, man, it's fun, it's great." Then he said, "Hey, you're in some
trouble, no, my
life is going well."
I said, "No, man, bro, everything is going well." I can
see your eyes. I said, "No, everything is
fine." Then all this talk happened. If there is something wrong, tell me,
brother, I'm for you. I
said, "Yes, bro." Then everything is over.
I went home. I sat in the car. I
felt that I was sad. That impression was
visible on my face. I was sad.
Why did you talk to me like this? That was my
first impression. I said, "
Why are you a loser?"  This is because
he had to record everything, that is, if he says yes, then stand up,
I will come with three cameras,
then I thought about the answer.
When I go to his podcast, he will
ask, "What is your pain? If I
show you something, I will say
no,
it is a chip." Has Viraj ever thought about death? He
talks like this. I see an image. It is a little bit of him.
He is giving his reflection to others. The poor thing is that
he is sad himself. Nothing else.
This will be cut. I think. No, no, it will not happen. I will let him take it. He
understands some Gujarati. So,
Ranveer is a native of Alawadi. Ranveer is a native of Nadiad. Nadiad is a little bit of
Nadiad. Nadiad is also a native of Nadiad. But this movie was also
shot near Nadiad. There is a village called Vaso. Hey, it was
shot in Vaso. Someone from Vaso is a
thief from Dakor. Oh, it is
not right next to it.
Yes, if you ask Vaso, Naliad comes up with something like Dakor.
Yes, Dakor is close to Vaso. No, it is not far from Vaso.  No,
go out for a walk in the car one day, it's
so close, it's far, it's far, it's far,
yes, but the best part about Vaso is that
those people are used to shooting there, yes,
and that's why we people, Kamthan, also shoot there,
Kamthan, B, shot there, Manto, also shot there, are
we used to shooting in Ahmedabad or Mumbai, if people are shooting in Ahmedabad or Mumbai,
what is it, then
those people, well, from which side will we go,
good people and I flip, why are these people
good, give them a few insults, then it will seem
that the shooting people have come here too, there are no very nice, very good people,
but if
you want actual rudeness, then
when there is a match in Ahmedabad,
you will know, you are not a big man, you are a
big man, I went to watch the match yesterday,
GT CSK, GT Rock Guys, yes, sorry,
Mumbai, Mumbai, our condition is a bit bad
these days, these days
Sorry this season the
world has been shaken so
what happened then that last time
Mumbai Indians are seen on the points table
[praise]
I thought it was an ant or something oh but no just a
little bit there if there is GT I
have only one comeback five cups we
have how many one minute one minute just
came in childhood we people have been playing for years yes so how
many years have you been playing IPL is
doing this wrong now percentage this is wrong match
no but yesterday I was going to watch the match and
I put it in a service line and
I was going right side in the service line
and then a person came from this side a
husband wife on an Activa from the footpath understood aya
and got down in front of me and cut to cut
bomber to bumper traffic so I made a gap in between
now this side there was a whole lane of two wheelers in
front of me I put my car and
Activa in between because he had to
go there I honked then he  He
looked at me like this, as if it was my fault,
I honked the horn, so I honked a little longer, then
he took out the key and sat down,
how many times will I honk? His
wife took out the paper from the dikem, had breakfast,
took the light and turned it on
with me. Once this happened in
Ahmedabad, when I had just
come back from the valley, I came in my car, if it was an
MMH car, then what is the rule of the Pakesh police
that it is their car, then
I don't know, if it is a gj car, then I
don't know the reference, but gj means
Baroda, if there is any other car except here, then they will
catch it, like everyone has something in their
dikem, yes, I did
n't know about it, then no one used to wear a helmet,
here, I was a
rebel that
everything was going on like this, I
stopped my car and my brother was driving and
I  Passengers have a habit in Mumbai that the
passengers there do not wear seat belts.
I used to have a habit of not wearing them.
Then the police stopped me and said, "
Come on, what are you doing? This is all illegal."
I said, "Oh, but he is not wearing a helmet, but
catch him. This is more legal.
Who is it now?
That man will not catch him. In this, I want to
see you. First,
he told me that. Then, whether we are wearing it
or
not. I do not want to talk about your safety.
That man told me this. I flipped.
Like you, I was so confused. At that time, yes,
that man. I said, "The one with the helmet is
not wearing a helmet. Catch him. Do you
know that he is going to get breakfast?"
I said, "Catch him."
Sir, you are a loser. I have never heard of
a man who went to get breakfast and
fell and died.
Tell me how many times. I will not be able to handle this.
I am dying now."  If he is gone, it would be
sad for the people who are eating breakfast, that poor man, that
uncle has passed away, the ayah of the pauwa bi,
then he has to open the tin of that ben,
take the pickle and thepala from him and sit there, that
this is our symbol of the
shop, I too, here on the expressway,
whenever I enter, our car stops and stops
and once,
Vidya was also with me, my wife, we
showed her the tin, we
asked where the lady constable was, give us two minutes, they kept
us standing there for 10 minutes,
then the ayah or the lady constable is not there right now,
but we will check the bags of the men only,
I knew whose bag the stock is in, so
I said, check everything except this, then when I
open the bag and find
Vidya's stuff in it, that brother
looks at me, this is yours,
I said yes, I also get 36D,
how about once with me  It
happened in Vadodara itself that
there is a spot where checking is done, it is
outside the city limits, so they catch us, we used to come after
finishing a shoot
and all the equipment of the shoot and everything was lying inside,
water bottles, that is,
empty water bottles from the entire shoot, and those
people used to stop us, I don't know what
fun we had, it was the time, we used to have fun,
now I deliberately started
acting drunk and stopped them,
what should I do, I said, sir, we have come
from the shoot and for a minute, come to the side and
check and there were 22 bottles inside,
they sniffed everything, poor thing, sorry sir, you
smelled your bottles, I caught me once,
come closer to my mouth and sniff
here, open your mouth, breathe, I said,
doctor, what is the police, then I
smelled it, I had come to the ground here, I smelled it from the
western, I know it's a joke  There is a
pipe, there is a pipe system, there is a pipe
The colors and shooting were good, the video did
not work and
then and then he left it in his car and it was left for
15-16 days and we forgot about it and
here it is near Vishala for checking
and we said, "Check it out, there is
nothing, open the trunk and it is just a dagger, come on, come in."
I said, "If we have committed murder,
why do we leave the paddle open next to the CNG bottle? If we have committed
murder, running away in CNG is not a
small thing. It will
take 10 minutes after 200 kilometers, sir. Now, all those people, get
out of the car. Everyone, get out of the car."
Then I told you that I do not
drink, but when the friends who were with me
came from Gujarat and Mumbai, I knew that I would never meet them in
my car in my life.
My brother and I have never drunk. When they
came, I showed them the other side of the car and said, "We have done whatever we have to do to check." Then I tore off all the
seat covers and
opened everything for you.  I called B and said, "Is
this a problem with me? After
doing everything, I
found a can from somewhere inside the step. Now my
fiancée is an EPA. I knew this,
but I didn't know that she would have opened the step inside the car and
drank it like this. That's why
I was so angry. Go do whatever you want to do. I have nothing. I am a Gujarati comedian  I
heard about Baiting for the first time but I think one of the only people
about whom I was wrong in the beginning
is Viraj Gilani and after years today
when I see his progress
and what I think is art without consistency
and discipline is not
and that is the thing I learn from Viraj to this day
that being consistent is
a discipline in content
creation in art and that has been absolutely amazing
for Viraj Gilani so genuinely till today I also told him
multiple types and whenever I am in problem or anything goes wrong in my
life in terms of content creation anything in life also I think that
once in a while we should take Mananbhai's advice
and it is not that we
sit and lick others but genuinely
and when  I said that the liquor
thing was caught, then I
called you Govinda, he called me in my name too
and I cursed you that you
take so little, yes, what is the issue of money, yes,
talk about money
[laughter]
Money is an empty confession.
When I saw Viraj in Jawaan, I did
n't recognize him for 30 seconds because he was so full of cheek, like he had stuck a
blade inside his cheek and rubbed it.
Then it took two seconds. I said, this
is Virajbhai, what did you know about Jawaan?
You saw Jawaan and I did
n't want to be a wife in that.
Because the reason is, my
role was for half an hour, The Moment When You See Me Till The End
I'm Just There. I shot Shahrukh Khan
and ran away. And a lot of
things happened like I shot for 15 days and I was
very excited that now my time has come,
now I have come in Jawaan. Everything happened
then I blinked.  Which is my favorite
I said today is the premiere let's go
see it I said ok done done sat got
ready and went wearing expensive expensive clothes then I
sat like this then I said
if Palak will come now I came Palak is after this and this
scene was not
Palak I don't mind if we have someone
now it is and in the next scene last then
what am I doing I killed it I am done
Virat movie was
a shocker for me you did
n't take it till here
so that was red chillies and it seemed spicy
oh but now it is now coming bright
see brother how is your
Gujarati experience in
comparison of national or in front of audience and even
in general work ethics and work ethics wise I have realized that
someone makes some mistake and in
life while shooting or something then
those people should come with the same pattern
thing Gujarati I said oh
but change  Do it and come to Gujarat.
Gujarat, oh Gujarati cinema should come.
I said, do it and this is ours. This is
generally I want to tell everyone that we are watching here or here.
We are
very much in the West and many
things like in terms of Gujarati cinema.
We respect Bollywood first. We
respect Bollywood first.
So we went to the theater.
When I went to the
theater, all the posters in Gujarat were
Kareena Kapoor and Prabhas. We did
not have any Malhar. We did not have any photo of Yash. No one
should be like us. This is a good learning which I got to know that as a like we all have to
respect
artists as much as we respect South
Indian actors. We
put up posters of Gujarat but there were no actors of ours. So that
thing hit me very hard.  I told him
that if all this should change, then
this is the thing for you. Please, when you are going,
please, let us support the cinema,
not because my movie is coming, my movie will come and go. I
know
what one of those sitting in 300 thinks.
What if the picture is good?
I heard his thoughts here.
I also heard his thoughts. This will happen only with support.
So this is what I wanted to give out a
message. Genuinely, no, it will change. I think a
little bit has changed. Now,
after seeing many posters of Three Eka,
posters of Samandar have also been put up. It has started to go. No, but you have lost quite a bit. Quite some weight. That's great. What is the secret? I am going to
Cannes Film Festival. For the first
time, I just wanted to look slimy. There was nothing else
and no.  No, it is not called Cannes in
Gujarat, it is called Cannes. I just
found out. Vidyabha told me inside. Not Cannes. Nice. Nice. Journey. Nice. From that Cannes to
this
Cannes. You people called me to kill me.
I
feel like you are praising me so much. Why are you doing this?
But Viraj. Viraj is super sweet. Congratulations
to you. Viraj. Thank you for
the first debut film. And because of you, there are
more posters, banners and
hoardings. People in Gujarati
cinema should praise your picture and all the
best to you. Viraj and hopefully we will see you soon on a
stage in Ahmedabad with your show. Congratulations
[Music]